# DARCY LAUDER PROFESSIONAL FULL STACK

- DEVELOPMENT

   darcy.lauder@shaw.ca
- **4**036905193
- ♥ Calgary, AB
- in darcylauder
- c deke76

Full stack web developer focused on helping clients and companies implement their vision for distributed applications using HTML interfaces and various back end data structures. I have worked with small teams implementing features via React, NestJS, Python and Golang (using the Fabric SDK for blockchain and been introduced to Agile working methodologies.

### **Skills**

#### WEB DEVELOPMENT

**Javascript** 

Typescript

Ruby

Rails

Golang Blockchain (Fabric)

React

NestJS

Python

Microservices

Monoliths

PostgreSQL

### **Education**

Southern Alberta Institute of Technology Electronics Engineering Technologist

Lighthouse Labs Full Stack Web Developer Jan. 2022 to Apr. 2022

lan. 2001 to Dec. 2003

### **Employment**

### **Cultivated Code**

Junior Web Developer

June 2022 to Apr. 2023

Worked with a small remote team to develop SprintMetrics and LevelSight using Javascript, React, Tailwinds, NestJS and Express as well as confidential client work utilizing Golang, Python and Blockchain. Responsible for developing code according to the functional requirements as described by our clients.

#### Guillevin International

Calgary, AB Jan. 2019 to Dec. 2021

Technical Sales Representative

Managed a Calgary client base centered around oil and gas producers, OEM fabricators, pipeline companies and EPCs to provide automation centric solutions using the Schneider, SICK and Turck products lines. Primary point of contact for PLC, sensor and software questions from the assigned customer base. Responsible for maintaining current customer revenue while finding new growth opportunities with existing and new customers.

Terago Networks

Calgary, AB

Channel Partner

Worked with partners to provide private and public cloud solutions, colocation services and internet connectivity. Primary point of contact for partners to resolve issues as well as help them with new business development and facilitate communication with direct sales team. Responsible to maintain corporate partnership and revenue from small to mid-sized IT Managed providers.

Vanko Analytics Ltd.

Calgary, AB

Sept. 2016 to Nov. 2018

**Technical Sales Representative** 

Sept. 2012 to Nov. 2015 ocess instrumentation solutions

Managed a south east Alberta and south west Saskatchewan territy. Worked with customers to provide process instrumentation solutions to measure level, pressure, flow and fluid/gas compositions. Responsible to maintain current customr base while prospecting for new opportunities with EPC's, fabricators and end users.

#### Mico-Watt Control Devices

Calgary, AB

Technical Sales Representative

June 2011 to Sept. 2012

Managed a territory in south central Alberta. Worked with customers to provide instrumentation solutions centered around fire and gas detection in primarily oil and gas settings. Responsible for growing sales within assigned account base while displacing competitor offerings with potential customers.

### **Projects**

SprintMetrics.id

June 2022 to Apr. 2003

SprintMetrics helps you run more meaningful, collaborative sprints by leveraging data and industry best practices to create accountability and momentum helping you add features, fix issues and speed time to market.

LevelSight.io Jan. 2023 to Apr. 2003

Integration and gamification of pull requests with Slack in order to remove bottlenecks and increase team performance.

URL shortener built using server side scriting with the Express.js framework

Feb. 2022 to Feb. 2022

Basic Twitter clone built using SPA, Express and jQuery with cookies functionality

Mar. 2022 to Mar. 2022

Feb. 2022 to Feb. 2022

Feb. 2022 to Mar. 2022

Pantryful

Food management application buit with a React front end accessing a Rails server with the help of external API's.

Scheduler
React.js SPA application with RDBMS back end to book appointments between students and interviewers.

Hockey - recreational · Forward/defense

## Volunteering

Play hockey with various teams.

Activities

Girls Hockey Calgary · Treasurer - GHC U11 Flames Calgary

CWC Sea Lions · Group Liason

Sept. 2022 to June 2023

Calgary

Communicated with coaches and board when parents had a questions with regards to programming, meets or social events.